Kevin Honnoll

617.335.5750 kevin.honnoll@gmail.com kevinhonnoll.com linkedin.com/in/kevinhonnoll

Full Stack Web Developer passionate about chasing creative vision, building things to better people's lives, and leaving a positive mark on the world. Former Registered Nurse ready for unexpected challenges, multidisciplinary teamwork, and careful communication. Former Audio Engineer with a love for tinkering, making things, finding beauty. Motivated by learning, seeking solutions, solving problems, and helping others do the same. Currently seeking opportunities to continue growing my skills by making web applications.

Skills

React | Ruby on Rails | JavaScript | HTML5 | CSS3 | Materialize | Bootstrap | ¡Query | GitHub | Heroku

Web Development Experience

Software Engineering Immersive Program, 3/2019 - 8/2019

500 program hours over 24-weeks of full-stack experience in HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, jQuery, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, NodeJS, React, Git, Github, and Agile/Scrum. Course projects, the bulk of which were completed in one-week sprints:

Van Builder - Planner/tracker for camper van conversions.

Made with React, Router, Reactstrap, Node, Express, Knex, bcrypt, and httpOnly cookies. Record Collector - Catalog for vinyl albums.

Made with HTML, CSS, Materialize, Node.js, Mongoose, Express, EJS, and bcrypt. Beer Hunter - Search for beers, view details, and add selections to a favorites list. Made with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, and jQuery UI.

Professional Experience

Boston Children's Hospital | Boston, MA Staff Nurse, Urology Foundation (2012-2019)

Elliot Hospital | Manchester, NH Staff Nurse, Fitch Unit (2010-2012)

Education

General Assembly | Software Engineering Immersive Program | Remote Bachelor of Science in Nursing | MA College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences | Manchester, NH Bachelor of Business Administration | Belmont University | Nashville, TN

Interests

Endurance Running | Including the Boston Marathon and the New York City Marathon Music | Collaborating, making noise, and recording since grade school Camper Van Conversion | Off-grid living